<resources>
    <string name="app_name">TxtNet Browser</string>
    <string name="check_connection">Please check your internet connection.</string>
    <string name="forward_arrow">Forward Arrow</string>
    <string name="go_button">GO</string>
    <string name="descr_overflow_button">Options</string>
    <string name="is_accessed">isAccessed</string>
    <string name="phone_number">phoneNumber</string>
    <string name="default_phone">+18884842216</string>
    <string name="optin_confirmation_terms">
        "By using this app, you agree to accept its Terms of Service, described below.\n\n"
        "TL;DR: TxtNet Browser app servers won\'t text you unless you specifically make a web request. The developer(s) of TxtNet Browser ("the app") do not seek to sell or give away data in any form by offering this service. However, the developer would ideally not like to be charged for a crime by facilitating requests to illegal services, so you're on the hook for your own requests.\n\n"
        "THESE TERMS ONLY APPLY TO TxtNet Server INSTANCES HOSTED BY THE DEVELOPERS OF THE APP, AND THE DEVELOPERS ARE NOT RESPONSIBLE FOR NOR HAVE ANY CONTROL OVER THIRD PARTY SERVERS.\n"
        "By accepting these Terms of Service, you (the user) agree that by pressing the \"Enter\" key or the \"Search\" icon in this app, the app will send a varying amount of text messages to the specified phone number selected as the user's current \"Server Phone Number\" (referred to hereafter as \"the phone number\").\n"
        "Users opt-in to receiving SMS messages to SMS messages when you agree to these terms by pressing \"I Accept\". SMS exchanges are initiated by the user, and run for the duration of the request, which is typically (but not guaranteed to be) under one minute."
        "No further SMS messages are initiated by the phone number until another opt-in request is made by the user (noted by the submission of a request).\n\n"

        "The phone number hoster is not liable for any effects of receiving SMS messages from the phone number, such as an increase in storage utilization or app crashes."
        "You agree that user data (your phone number and request URL) will be stored by the phone number hoster, until they clear their SMS message history. The developers' server instance automatically clears SMS logs at least every 30 days.\n\n"
        "If a user makes a request to a website that infringes on the laws of the jurisdiction where the server resides physically, the user, and not the server hoster, shall be deemed legally responsible for all repercussions when possible to the fullest extent of the law."
        "The developers recommend that SMS logs are cleared frequently by the server hoster so that relevant authorities cannot enforce unjust censorship laws upon either the user or the server hoster for accessing websites (specifically, those legal under U.S. law as of 2022, but not legal under the laws of the server's current jurisdiction.)"
        "Because the app is open source, the developers of the app cannot guarantee that user privacy and SMS limitations are guaranteed when connecting to a server phone number provided by a third party source.\n"
        "If you are concerned about sending SMS messages to an unknown party, we encourage you to host your own TxtNet Server instance.\n\n"
    </string>
    <string name="accept">I Accept</string>
    <string name="cancel">Close App</string>
    <string name="is_tosaccepted">isTosAccepted</string>
    <string name="server_description">The TxtNet Browser server uses the device\'s internet connection to communicate websites to clients through SMS.</string>
    <string name="server_started">Started</string>
    <string name="server_stopped">Stopped</string>
    <string name="title_activity_server_picker">Select a phone number</string>
    <string name="large_text">
        "Material is the metaphor.\n\n"

        "A material metaphor is the unifying theory of a rationalized space and a system of motion."
        "The material is grounded in tactile reality, inspired by the study of paper and ink, yet "
        "flexibility of the material creates new affordances that supercede those in the physical "
        "world, without breaking the rules of physics.\n"
       "interact, and exist in space and in relation to each other. Realistic lighting shows "
        "seams, divides space, and indicates moving parts.\n\n"

        "Bold, graphic, intentional.\n\n"

        "Components with responsive elevations may encounter other components as they move between "
        "their resting elevations and dynamic elevation offsets. Because material cannot pass "
        "through other material, components avoid interfering with one another any number of ways, "
        "whether on a per component basis or using the entire app layout.\n"
        "On a component level, components can move or be removed before they cause interference. "
        "For example, a floating action button (FAB) can disappear or move off screen before a "
        "user picks up a card, or it can move if a snackbar appears.\n"
        "On the layout level, design your app layout to minimize opportunities for interference. "
        "For example, position the FAB to one side of stream of a cards so the FAB won’t interfere "
        "when a user tries to pick up one of cards.\n\n"
    </string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="add_server">Add A Server</string>
    <string name="start_service_string">Start Service</string>
    <string name="populate_server_hint">eg. +16125551234</string>
    <string name="button_save">Save</string>
    <string name="empty_not_saved">Phone Number not saved because it is empty.</string>
    <string name="title_activity_shizuku_incompatible">ShizukuIncompatibleActivity</string>
    <string name="shizuku_incompatible_description">
        Sorry, but it appears that your device isn\'t compatible with granting permissions via the Shizuku app. You can still create a TxtNet server instance, but you will need a computer with adb installed.
        Once you install adb, connect your phone via USB to your computer and enable USB debugging in your phone\'s settings. Then, run the following commands through adb shell:\n\n
        \'settings put global sms_outgoing_check_max_count 1000000\' \n\n
        \'settings put global sms_outgoing_check_interval_ms 30000\' \n\n
        Once both commands have been run, click the button below to continue.
        </string>
    <string name="shizuku_incompatible_continue">Reload module</string>
    <string name="request_sms_outgoing_exceeded_error">Error: Request Exceeded Max SMS Limit</string>
    <string name="newServerInfoStr">Input a phone number that you would like to connect to.\nThe number must be hosting a TxtNet Server instance.\nNOTE: If you do not wish to use client features and only wish to host a server,\nplease input an fake number such as\n+15555555555</string>
</resources>