<resources>
    <string name="app_name">TxtNet Browser</string>
    <string name="check_connection">Please check your internet connection.</string>
    <string name="forward_arrow">Forward Arrow</string>
    <string name="go_button">GO</string>
    <string name="descr_overflow_button">Options</string>
    <string name="is_accessed">isAccessed</string>
    <string name="phone_number">phoneNumber</string>
    <string name="default_phone">+18884842216</string>
    <string name="optin_confirmation_terms">
        Twilio (the provider of the server phone number that I am using) requires a Terms of Service in order to keep my toll-free server number functional.
\n\n
        TL;DR: I don\'t want your data and the app won\'t text you unless you specifically make a web request! I have no reason to pester you with texts outside of giving you the website you requested in the first place. I\'m not looking to make a profit or give away/sell user data by offering this service.
\n\n
        By accepting these Terms of Service, you (the user) agree that by pressing the \"Enter\" key or the \"Search\" icon in this app, the app will send a varying amount of text messages to the specified phone number listed under the \"Change Server Phone Number\" option (referred to hereafter as \"the phone number\")
        Users opt-in to receiving SMS messages to SMS messages when you agree to these terms by pressing \"I Accept\". SMS exchanges are initiated by the user, and run for the duration of the request, which is typically under one minute. No further SMS messages are initiated by the phone number until another opt-in request is made by the user (noted by the submission of a request). An opt-out button is also made available inside the app which sends the text \“STOP\” to the toll-free number on your behalf.
\n\n
        The number of text messages sent to the phone number is a direct result of the length of URL you request, shown in the URL/search bar. For example, URLs over 200 characters long are likely to be split into 2 text messages.
        By initiating contact in sending (or allowing TxtNet Browser to send) an SMS to the phone number, you agree to receive between 1 (one) and 100 (one hundred) SMS messages from the phone number in the form of an encoded web site. Each request to the phone number constitutes one \'conversation\' which includes your implied consent and proof of consent.
        You may reply STOP at any time to stop receiving SMS messages from the phone number. The \"stop\" icon of TxtNet browser automatically sends this text on your behalf.
\n\n
        The phone number hoster is not liable for any effects of receiving SMS messages from the phone number, such as an increase in storage utilization or app crashes.
        The phone number hoster will keep a \"timestamp of when the customer completed a sign-up flow.\" as required by Twilio\'s Toll-Free number messaging policy, available at https://www.twilio.com/legal/messaging-policy
\n\n
        You agree that user data (such as phone number and request URL) will not be stored by the phone number hoster unless an error occurs, in which case it may be logged for 30 days to assist in resolving bugs.

    </string>
    <string name="accept">I Accept</string>
    <string name="cancel">Close App</string>
    <string name="is_tosaccepted">isTosAccepted</string>
    <string name="server_description">The TxtNet Browser server uses the device\'s internet connection to communicate websites to clients through SMS.</string>
    <string name="server_started">Started</string>
    <string name="server_stopped">Stopped</string>
    <string name="title_activity_server_picker">Select a phone number</string>
    <string name="large_text">
        "Material is the metaphor.\n\n"

        "A material metaphor is the unifying theory of a rationalized space and a system of motion."
        "The material is grounded in tactile reality, inspired by the study of paper and ink, yet "
        "technologically advanced and open to imagination and magic.\n"
        "Surfaces and edges of the material provide visual cues that are grounded in reality. The "
        "use of familiar tactile attributes helps users quickly understand affordances. Yet the "
        "flexibility of the material creates new affordances that supercede those in the physical "
        "world, without breaking the rules of physics.\n"
        "The fundamentals of light, surface, and movement are key to conveying how objects move, "
        "interact, and exist in space and in relation to each other. Realistic lighting shows "
        "seams, divides space, and indicates moving parts.\n\n"

        "Bold, graphic, intentional.\n\n"

        "The foundational elements of print based design typography, grids, space, scale, color, "
        "and use of imagery guide visual treatments. These elements do far more than please the "
        "eye. They create hierarchy, meaning, and focus. Deliberate color choices, edge to edge "
        "imagery, large scale typography, and intentional white space create a bold and graphic "
        "interface that immerse the user in the experience.\n"
        "An emphasis on user actions makes core functionality immediately apparent and provides "
        "waypoints for the user.\n\n"

        "Motion provides meaning.\n\n"

        "Motion respects and reinforces the user as the prime mover. Primary user actions are "
        "inflection points that initiate motion, transforming the whole design.\n"
        "All action takes place in a single environment. Objects are presented to the user without "
        "breaking the continuity of experience even as they transform and reorganize.\n"
        "Motion is meaningful and appropriate, serving to focus attention and maintain continuity. "
        "Feedback is subtle yet clear. Transitions are efﬁcient yet coherent.\n\n"

        "3D world.\n\n"

        "The material environment is a 3D space, which means all objects have x, y, and z "
        "dimensions. The z-axis is perpendicularly aligned to the plane of the display, with the "
        "positive z-axis extending towards the viewer. Every sheet of material occupies a single "
        "position along the z-axis and has a standard 1dp thickness.\n"
        "On the web, the z-axis is used for layering and not for perspective. The 3D world is "
        "emulated by manipulating the y-axis.\n\n"

        "Light and shadow.\n\n"

        "Within the material environment, virtual lights illuminate the scene. Key lights create "
        "directional shadows, while ambient light creates soft shadows from all angles.\n"
        "Shadows in the material environment are cast by these two light sources. In Android "
        "development, shadows occur when light sources are blocked by sheets of material at "
        "various positions along the z-axis. On the web, shadows are depicted by manipulating the "
        "y-axis only. The following example shows the card with a height of 6dp.\n\n"

        "Resting elevation.\n\n"

        "All material objects, regardless of size, have a resting elevation, or default elevation "
        "that does not change. If an object changes elevation, it should return to its resting "
        "elevation as soon as possible.\n\n"

        "Component elevations.\n\n"

        "The resting elevation for a component type is consistent across apps (e.g., FAB elevation "
        "does not vary from 6dp in one app to 16dp in another app).\n"
        "Components may have different resting elevations across platforms, depending on the depth "
        "of the environment (e.g., TV has a greater depth than mobile or desktop).\n\n"

        "Responsive elevation and dynamic elevation offsets.\n\n"

        "Some component types have responsive elevation, meaning they change elevation in response "
        "to user input (e.g., normal, focused, and pressed) or system events. These elevation "
        "changes are consistently implemented using dynamic elevation offsets.\n"
        "Dynamic elevation offsets are the goal elevation that a component moves towards, relative "
        "to the component’s resting state. They ensure that elevation changes are consistent "
        "across actions and component types. For example, all components that lift on press have "
        "the same elevation change relative to their resting elevation.\n"
        "Once the input event is completed or cancelled, the component will return to its resting "
        "elevation.\n\n"

        "Avoiding elevation interference.\n\n"

        "Components with responsive elevations may encounter other components as they move between "
        "their resting elevations and dynamic elevation offsets. Because material cannot pass "
        "through other material, components avoid interfering with one another any number of ways, "
        "whether on a per component basis or using the entire app layout.\n"
        "On a component level, components can move or be removed before they cause interference. "
        "For example, a floating action button (FAB) can disappear or move off screen before a "
        "user picks up a card, or it can move if a snackbar appears.\n"
        "On the layout level, design your app layout to minimize opportunities for interference. "
        "For example, position the FAB to one side of stream of a cards so the FAB won’t interfere "
        "when a user tries to pick up one of cards.\n\n"
    </string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="add_server">Add A Server</string>
    <string name="start_service_string">Start Service</string>
    <string name="populate_server_hint">Phone number...</string>
    <string name="button_save">Save</string>
    <string name="empty_not_saved">Phone Number not saved because it is empty.</string>
    <string name="title_activity_shizuku_incompatible">ShizukuIncompatibleActivity</string>
    <string name="shizuku_incompatible_description">
        Sorry, but it appears that your device isn\'t compatible with granting permissions via the Shizuku app. You can still create a TxtNet server instance, but you will need a computer with adb installed.
        Once you install adb, connect your phone via USB to your computer and enable USB debugging in your phone\'s settings. Then, run the following commands:
        \nsettings put global sms_outgoing_check_max_count 1000000 \n
        settings put global sms_outgoing_check_interval_ms 30000 \n
        Once both commands have been run, click the button below to continue.
        </string>
    <string name="shizuku_incompatible_continue">Restart App</string>
</resources>